[suspenseful music playing]
[overlapping conversations]
[cell phone chimes]
DO YOU HAVE ANYONE ELSE TO TALK TO?
I JUST WANT TO STOP BEING INVISIBLE.
[music grows ominous]
- [indistinct chatter distorts]
- [camera shutter clicks]
[muffled laughter]
[indistinct voices echoing]
[ominous music building]
[ominous music fades]
[footsteps approaching]
[Roberta, gently] Bebé.
Come on. You're gonna be late.
Don't give up. That's what they want.
What's going on?
What… What's this "us" and "them" about?
They're turning up the pressure.
To make us hand the business over.
But we will never cave in to them.
You will stay strong.
Away from Dídac.
[gentle music playing]
[Roberta] Come on.
Come on. I'll take you to school.
Like when you were little.
[footsteps fade]
[gentle music ends]
["La La La La LA" by Luwaks playing]
SARA'S BIRTHDAY PARTY
THEME?
GLITTER, YOUR BODY, AND SKIMPY CLOTHING
So for the party,
you just take some videos and selfies,
and they'll pay you for it?
- Bussin'.
- [Sara chuckles]
The birthday party's really just an excuse
to celebrate Iván moving in with us.
- And to cheer him up.
- [Raúl] That's right.
A great idea.
Some solid partying
could do you some good.
Even if it's to hide how broken you are.
Fake it till you make it, babies. [kisses]
[somber music playing]
[indistinct, excited chatter]
[music fades]
["La La La La LA" playing]
[Carmen] I think
Iván is going to this party.
You could go. Get to know him better.
Fuck. You gotta be kidding me.
Don't drag me into your bullshit.
Even if we came out of the same place,
Iván isn't my brother, okay?
Wouldn't you like to be a family,
the three of us?
So is it family,
or more the inheritance calling to you?
You don't have to say the first thought
that passes through your head.
Well, I said don't drag me into this.
Look, there he is. Go and tell him.
Say, "Hello. I'm your mother."
And get it over with.
You have a brain. Use it.
I can't be that straightforward.
We'll ease him into it
before spilling it all.
How would you feel if you had
a mother appear out of thin air?
I'd like if a normal one appeared.
Chloe, come on, dear.
We're a team.
Please. I can't do this without you.
Forget it. I'm out.
[door slams]
[hushed chatter]
[phone vibrates]
MOM: BEEN INVITED TO THE PARTY YET?
[Chloe sighs]
[quietly] What is this?
It's for Sonia.
It's a vintage device that plays music.
- [gentle music playing]
- I made her a playlist.
How do you share the songs on that?
[clicks tongue] That's not how it works.
- You don't share this. You use it to-
- [girl] Shh!
[quietly] I'll tell you later.
It's complicated.
What the hell?
PLAYLIST FOR CHLOE
I'm sorry. Can I help you?
Are you a child who needs some attention?
PLAYLIST ADDED TO YOUR MUSIC
Um, can I have that back?
Thank you.
[Eric] I shared a playlist with you.
So you can use your squatter songs
to conquer my heart?
To get to know you.
We can communicate through music.
There wasn't much talking
when we hooked up.
I'm sorry. Is that what you call it?
[scoffs] You don't talk,
but you tease, don't you?
Well, I tease 'cause the grand gestures
belong in rom-coms.
It's a small gesture.
We had chemistry with each other.
- [girl] Shh!
- [quietly] Hear that? Silence.
[whispers] Just so you know,
silence is my favorite music.
[somber music playing]
And I don't need to know anything more
about you after this bullshit.
- [indistinct chatter]
- [somber music fades]
[Chloe] Hey, listen. I'm sorry.
- [Iván] What for?
- [sighs]
Well, because I treated you
more like a Kleenex than a man,
and I went way overboard.
It's no big deal.
Honestly, at first I was up for it.
Then I wasn't,
but because of my own stuff.
- Not your fault.
- Yeah, but we know I went pretty hard.
- Yeah, you did. [laughs]
- [Chloe] Yeah.
I know it might not seem like it,
but I'm incredibly socially awkward.
With people,
I'm like a bull in a china shop, y'know?
I'm awful at making friends.
And at first impressions.
No one makes plans with me.
I don't get invited to-
Hey, come to Sara's birthday.
- [Chloe] Really?
- Of course.
I mean, sign me up.
But I wasn't invited by her.
Well, I live there, so you're invited.
Mm, great.
- Great.
- [Chloe] Okay.
- See you there.
- [Chloe] Yeah, awesome.
[footsteps fade]
MOM: YEAH, I WAS INVITED.
[phone chimes]
What really pisses me off is
that all this is driving me away from Isa.
And what does she have to do with it?
Luis, maybe I should use that app to talk
about my private life instead, y'know?
That's an option.
Although, I thought
you might wanna open up
to an actual human.
[hesitates] I appreciate it, really.
The other day, I was worked up.
But, um, I'd rather not talk about me
or my family.
[Luis] Hey.
Just so you know,
my door will always be open. [sighs]
[tense music playing]
[cell phone chimes]
[tense music continues playing]
Fuck.
[tense music fades slowly]
[clicks tongue]
- Is this yours?
- Oh, thank God.
- You left it in my office.
- Thanks, Luis.
No worries.
[unsettling music playing]
[cell phone chimes]
COME ON. TALK TO ME.
YOU NEED TO KNOW THE TRUTH
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
[unsettling music fades]
[footsteps approaching]
[whispering] It's so
we can listen to music.
And rewind. Go back in time. To before.
- [chuckles]
- Wow. How subtle.
In real life, you don't get any do-overs.
The other night, we got a do-over, right?
No, I'd call the other night a mistake.
[somber music playing]
[Nico sighs]
[teacher] All right, everyone.
To your seats, please.
Start opening the app.
[music fades]
Hey. Is that a mixtape?
- [Sonia] A what?
- [Omar chuckles]
May I?
Maybe you're not as alone
as you think, huh?
Who said I was alone?
My bad. That came across as creepy.
It's just, I've been watching you.
You and the other students.
Fuck. That sounded better in my head.
- What I-
- Calm down.
You're the guy
who runs the app, right? Omar, yeah?
- Nice to meet you.
- [Sonia] Likewise.
I'm Sonia.
It's cool someone around here cares.
You wouldn't happen to be looking
for a volunteer, would you?
- [Omar scoffs]
- No. I'm a really good helper.
And you could use someone
who's close to the students.
I appreciate the offer.
But I've already strayed
too far from protocol.
I was supposed to be doing this from afar.
If you watch us like that,
you're a creeper for sure.
No. No, no. It's not that.
I'm with Joel.
[exhales]
Sometimes helpers need help too.
- [tender music playing]
- [Sonia chuckles slightly]
[exhales]
[soft rock playing over headphones]
[Raúl] Brands have written to me,
saying they were impressed
with the party and clamoring for more.
I say, total success.
In the end, between the party
and the rent, we made a bunch of money.
You were right, hon.
Babe. Not here at school.
They've seen us half naked in our Stories.
Come on. One kiss.
Excuse me. Hi.
This room is for students and staff only.
- [scoffs] I'm her boyfriend.
- You go to school or work here?
[Raúl scoffs]
[tense music playing]
You think you're helping,
but this pisses him off more.
[Jessica sighs]
[tense music continues playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Hey. I need your full attention.
That goes for you in the showers too.
I'm gonna be teaching
a women's self-defense class.
It's extracurricular.
To sign up, let me know.
Tell me in person,
through WhatsApp, DM, however you like.
Every woman should take it.
'Cause there are a lot of wolves
in the forest.
And you need to be prepared.
[tense music fades]
- This is harassment, you know.
- [Jessica sighs]
No, I'm looking after a student
and following up. It's my job.
You're not interested in the classes?
I don't like violence.
Defense.
You might not like violence, but some do.
You need to make sure you're protected.
You misunderstood.
I understood you loud and clear.
Leaving Raúl is not an option.
It's not.
Then here are your options.
Stay with him and pray to whatever god
you choose that he will keep you safe.
Or you learn to defend yourself.
In case things go wrong.
When I lived through the same hell as you,
I chose the second one.
[tense music playing]
INTERMEDIARY: AS SOON AS
THE FIRST PAYMENT IS IN MY ACCOUNT,
I'LL ORDER THE EVICTION.
[cell phone chimes]
[tense music fades]
Hey, Mom.
Sweetheart. I just met with Virginia.
Are you coming home?
Nico, Eric, and I are going out.
[indistinct chatter]
[Catalina] You aren't going
to that social center, right?
- I don't know. Why?
- It's not safe.
- They're evacuating any moment now.
- C'mon!
I did what I could to prevent it,
but my hands are tied.
You aren't going. Promise me.
[tense music resumes]
[chatting inaudibly]
[tense music building]
WE'RE STAYING
ART AND HOUSING FOR ALL
OCCUPIED SOCIAL CENTER
[tense music fades]
SELF-MANAGED SOCIAL CENTER
[indistinct chatter]
[Nico] We should be at the party,
not here.
Phones there.
We're gonna have a meeting
to organize surveillance, okay?
Wait. Surveillance for what?
- [girl] The cops are outside.
- What?
- [police sirens wailing]
- [ "GREEKo FREAKo" by Sophiya playing]
♪ Uh, uh, uh, uh… ♪
LEAVE PHONES HERE
NEW MESSAGE
COME TO SARA'S PARTY.
WE CAN TALK ABOUT STARTING OVER.
Falling for a gift and a song?
Kinda dumb for a girl as smart as you.
I'm a human with emotions.
Squashing them won't make it easier.
Yeah.
Hey, this is a cool song.
Maybe add it to your playlist with Eric.
I got rid of it. I'm onto something else.
[energetic Greek music continues]
♪ Okay, I'm bilingual, okay? ♪
[Chloe] Hey!
What's the matter? What's wrong?
[Iván] Nothing. It's just,
all this is too much for me.
Well, drink this. Come on.
I don't know if it's a good idea
to get drunk with what I'm dealing with.
It makes sense you feel off,
with leaving your house and all.
I've moved tons of times
because of my mother,
and I know what it's like.
Yeah, but at least you have
your mother with you.
Alone, it's not the same.
[Chloe swallows]
Jesus, I'm sorry. [chuckles]
Not trying to be a dark cloud here, but-
[chuckling slightly] No, no.
You're not a dark cloud.
I used to move all the time with my dad.
But this time around
is way more difficult.
Yeah. I can imagine.
I mean, I can't imagine it,
but I'm trying to imagine.
It sounds really hard.
♪ Greek-o, freak-o… ♪
I won't be good company right now.
I'm heading to my room for a bit.
- See if I can get outta this funk.
- Okay.
- See you around.
- Later.
♪ Greek-o, freak-o… ♪
MOM: IVÁN'S BEEN THROUGH A LOT,
AND HE'S STILL SUFFERING.
LET'S LEAVE HIM ALONE.
[pen scratching]
[Isa, over headphones] You're crazy.
Why would my mother kill Amazona?
[Dídac] I don't know, Isa.
To drive us apart, I guess.
And it looks like it's working.
[Isa] And why should we believe
your psychopath brother?
'Cause he's family?
But we can't believe my mom? Is that it?
[Dídac] Well, my "psychopath brother"
also says your mother
was behind the shooting.
- Yeah. No, no.
- What?
- [Isa] No, honestly. I can't take this.
- I know it seems crazy.
- Isa, listen!
- [Isa] You need to leave.
[Dídac] It sounds crazy-
No, it doesn't sound that way.
It is crazy.
Yeah. I know that.
I don't know who did what.
I don't know who to believe either, Isa.
But you saw what happened
with Pau and your mother.
[knock on window]
[Dídac, on headphones]
But don't push me away, please.
We're fighting on the same team.
Don't let them come between us.
- Don't let them win.
- [somber music playing]
Maybe they're right,
and it's best that we don't stay together.
Then it sounds like they've already won.
Dammit.
- What's the matter?
- I think these two just broke up.
If they don't talk,
we don't get any intel on their families.
[partner] Well, hey. It's for the best.
They've just denied us
the court order for the wiretap.
[Luis sighs]
[exhales]
[somber music fades]
[scoffs] Are you going
as unicorn diarrhea?
[chuckles]
- [Joel] I'll take over at 12:00, okay?
- [Dalmar] Yeah, sure.
- Thought you were off today.
- He's covering my shift for a few hours.
That's all.
[door opens]
See? You're ditching work
to go to their parties.
What's next? Skipping class?
- Losing the scholarship?
- Sweetheart, you're antagonizing me.
- I'm not antagonizing you.
- Fuck! All day, nagging.
"Don't do this.
Or that either. Or Las Encinas."
Enough. I'm begging you. Get off my back.
If you trust me, you trust me.
[somber music playing]
Come with me tonight.
[Omar sighs]
Come with me. Come to the party,
and you'll see you don't have to worry.
I've gone to many of those parties.
And I have no business there.
Go.
Go and have fun.
[music fades]
["Dirty Diabla" by Lapili playing]
[Carmen] Hi. Good evening.
She's gotta be fucking kidding.
[Carmen] Hi, girls.
Oh my God. Gorgeous. Oh please. I love it.
Hello.
Why the fuck are you here?
You're not living if you don't crash
a good party now and then, dear.
No, Mom. You're leaving right now.
You have no interest
in helping me with your brother.
Oh my God, Mom.
Will you stop saying he's my brother?
Fine, whatever you say.
If you won't do your part,
get outta my way.
I'm gonna do my own thing. Stay out of it.
[Carmen] Whoo!
[Patrick on recording]
I refuse to lose you forever.
Even if it is necessary.
Let me live with the hope
that one day we will meet again.
Hey there.
Why are you all alone?
Ma'am, why are you here?
Oh, Iván. Please don't be so formal.
You and I are friends.
Aren't we?
- Well, um-
- Want some? Are you all right?
That voice message sounded very intense.
It is, yeah.
Or it was, I guess.
Some long-lost love?
Would that be why you're missing out
on your own party?
It's not my party.
Every party can be yours
if you put your mind to it, my dear boy.
Tell me about the message.
Who was it? Or who is it?
My ex.
- And the guy they say ran me over.
- Who says that?
The investigators.
And the evidence.
But I don't believe it.
[sighs] So I keep obsessing,
trying to figure out what really happened.
And what if the truth
isn't what you want it to be?
[sighs] Well, um… I don't know.
In this life, you shouldn't seek
the truth unless you're truly prepared.
Otherwise, don't pry.
If it isn't the answer I want, then…
I would never be the same.
- That's right.
- [gentle music playing]
My advice you haven't asked for…
Keep forging ahead
in the belief your boyfriend didn't do it.
And then you can let it go.
As long as you keep looking to the past,
asking questions
that are better left unsolved,
you're missing out on all
the other beautiful things in your life.
[sighs] I don't know
what those things are.
You'll see them. Trust me.
When you step out
from under the past's shadow,
that's when you'll see it.
Anyway, out there is a party
waiting for you with your name on it.
Quite literally.
[gentle music continues]
- [phone chimes]
- [Patrick] My only option is to disappear.
[sighs] Or that's what I'm told.
So, until we see each other again…
I love you. [sobs]
- [Patrick] I love you so much, Iván.
- I love you so much, Patrick.
DELETE MESSAGE
CANCEL - DELETE
DELETE
- [cell phone chimes]
- [upbeat dance music playing]
My own mother didn't come.
I don't know why yours did.
She's my guest. Don't worry, okay?
I mean, they both are.
They're helping me a lot.
Don't worry about it. That's what matters.
And forgive Sara.
We've been stressed,
taking on the role of party organizers.
It's all good. Okay? Cheers.
- Happy birthday!
- [Iván] Want a drink? Okay.
- Hi. Chin-chin.
- Cheers.
- Wanna dance?
- [Chloe] Uh-uh.
Later.
Okay. Later.
[Carmen] Look at him. How happy he is.
It's doing him some good,
having us fluttering around.
Congrats. Mission accomplished.
So now you can leave.
Hey. Relax. It's all good.
I wanna see you dance.
I wanna see you laugh.
You know what, Mom?
If you could've,
you probably would've also abandoned me.
- Hey, hey, hey. What's going on?
- [Chloe] Hmm.
My dear, with Iván,
my heart was shattered.
Then you came along
and gave me another chance.
A consolation prize. Is that it?
You felt guilty for abandoning him,
and you had me as penance.
If you had kept him,
I wouldn't even exist. I know that.
Look at me, baby. Look at me.
You're the most important thing
in my life.
Hear me? The most important thing.
I want to give you a better future.
All right, well then, can we get
out of here and go back home?
- Oh no.
- Together?
I've been making such good progress.
- But you can leave if you want to, 'kay?
- [Chloe sighs]
["One to the Other" by Wolf & Cub playing]
[energetic piano intro playing]
[music building]
[Carmen sighs]
I told you beautiful things
would happen, right?
Well, there's one.
♪ Into the air ♪
♪ Into the air
I said it's not good for your head… ♪
What's up?
I know I shouldn't,
but I have to tell you,
you look beautiful.
♪ Into the air ♪
♪ Into the air, into the air… ♪
Dídac, you're just making this harder.
I need space.
Respect my boundaries, please.
♪ Into the air, I come ♪
♪ Oh… ♪
What happened? Something wrong?
Nothing's gone right or wrong, y'know?
Long story short, we're not together.
In fact…
- My dear! Everyone!
- [music stops]
- Hello! How are you? Time-out.
- [murmuring]
Uh, for all of you who are gossiping
and staring, let me confirm, okay?
Dídac and I are no more.
Now, to what matters. My love?
Cheers to Sara, my dears!
[guests cheer]
["One to the Other" continues playing]
You were a little dramatic out there.
[Isa, over headphones]
Oh, come on. It had to be believable.
If nobody knows we're together,
no one can split us up.
Wait. Can I tell you something?
Today, earlier, when we argued,
I felt I lost you.
Are you still doing the wiretap?
Luis, they denied the injunction.
Yeah. Yeah, Luena. I'm aware.
It's illegal.
[Luis clicks tongue, scoffs]
[Isa] I started thinking, and we usually
take the people closest to us for granted.
And today, I was scared.
So I won't push you away,
but we're gonna have to play stupid.
Until we can figure out this drama
between our two families.
- Sure. Yeah. Makes total sense.
- [Isa] Mm-hmm?
- Yeah.
- It does, yeah.
- [Dídac] Mm.
Anything for you, baby.
Baby? I'm dying. [giggles]
[kissing continues on headphones]
What's goin' on?
- Huh?
- [Luena] Hmm?
Okay. That's enough.
I'm done for the day.
[sirens wailing]
[crowd clamoring]
[indistinct police radio chatter]
[squatters shouting indistinctly]
- [man 1 shouts]
- [man 2] Fuck you!
- Go to hell!
- [man 1] Go home!
- [woman 1] Get outta here!
- [man 2] Leave us alone!
[woman 2] Sons of bitches!
[indistinct shouting continues]
They can't enter just yet,
but they're here to try to remove us.
- [Eric] Sons of bitches!
- What the fuck are you doing?
- [Eric] Chill. Just don't hit 'em.
- Hey. We didn't agree to assault, Eric.
We're defending this place.
We can't go until we kick them out.
[Nico] I'm outta here.
- [man 3] Get outta here, pig!
- [indistinct shouting]
- [woman 3] Get outta here!
- [woman 4] Get out!
[sirens wailing below]
[Eric] Cuz!
Hey. Be careful.
Go through the back. It's safer.
["Un día punk" by Juana Molina playing]
NEW MESSAGE
NO BATTERY
Oh shit.
[police and squatters shouting]
POLICE
Motherfuckers!
[laughs]
[Eric shouts]
[punk rock music building]
[riot shield bangs]
NO TO SPECULATION
- [Eric grunts]
- [chair clatters]
[Rocío] Fuck the police!
[punk rock song fades]
[Eric] Grab something.
They can't see us wearing
the same outfits.
[sighs] And what if we had hurt someone?
It still feels contradictory
to use force as a form of protection.
Contradictions aren't always bad.
You face them when you do brave things.
Oh, speaking of… contradictions,
why is it
you keep criticizing Las Encinas,
yet like someone like Chloe?
[sighs] She isn't what I thought she was.
But Las Encinas isn't either.
- Not entirely.
- Oh, no?
[Eric] No.
I thought it would be all materialism
and posers.
But I didn't think
I'd find someone like you.
[gentle music playing]
You are the only person
at that school who dares to be real.
Even my cousin,
after all he's been through,
just wants to fit in with all them.
Everyone wants to fit in.
I don't. At least,
not where they tell me to.
- Me neither.
- [Eric chuckles]
Although, today, for the first time
in a long time, I felt like I belonged.
[Eric chuckles]
[music grows tense]
What's wrong?
Your tattoo. I just noticed it.
- It's a tattoo. That's all.
- I know what it means.
[siren wailing]
[Eric] Come on, move!
["Ride" by Johnny Mafia playing]
[protestors chanting indistinctly]
[Eric] Let's go!
[chanting continues]
- ♪ I don't even care ♪
- [Eric] Shit. Other way.
♪ I feel I need you ♪
♪ I don't even care ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
Let's go!
["Ride" grows louder]
- ♪ Ride! ♪
- [squatter grunting]
♪ Ride! ♪
- ♪ Ride! ♪
- [squatter groaning]
♪ I do need you ♪
♪ Going through my mind ♪
- ♪ I do need you… ♪
- Hey! Hey!
[both grunting]
♪ I do really care ♪
♪ Na, na, na ♪
- [gun fires]
- [music stops]
- [high-pitched ringing]
- [Rocío panting, echoing]
[clamoring fades]
[tense music playing]
[whistle blows]
[cop 1] Huh? Tough guy?
- I'm innocent! Wait, I didn't do anything!
- [cop 2] Sure you are.
- Get in the damn van.
- Please, let me go! Eric!
- Eric!
- [somber music playing]
[breathing shakily]
[distant shouting fades]
[somber music dissipates]
- [ "Ghost of Arms" by Curses playing]
- [indistinct chatter]
[Iván] Everything okay?
Yeah. Waiting on a text from Omar.
And why didn't he come?
[exhales] Look, I mean,
I don't wanna ruin your night, Iván.
You're not ruining anything at all.
And If you wanna talk about it,
I'll be here.
Mm. Okay.
We'll tell each other shit
under one condition.
What?
We have to be dancing.
Well, let's dance. [chuckles]
["Ghost of Arms" continues]
♪ If I could resist… ♪
[Joel] I totally get Omar's traumatized
and hasn't been able to get over it,
but he should understand that getting
into Las Encinas was kind of a big deal.
♪ Far away from home ♪
♪ Far away from… ♪
[Joel] And what's wrong
with changing? Huh?
Why do I have to settle
for a life that's completely shitty?
♪ If your love was real… ♪
[Iván] Deleting the voice message
was hard for me.
But you can't live in the past.
Got that right.
♪ I won't be there
When the summer's gone… ♪
[Iván] I mean, that's life.
Changing from one moment to the next.
Look at me.
All we're able to do
is look ahead to the future.
♪ That you were not being you… ♪
- And enjoy the moments in between.
- [Joel] Like this one.
♪ Our time is gone ♪
♪ Now I know our time is gone ♪
["Ghost of Arms" continues]
[sighs]
♪ Now I know our time is gone ♪
- ♪ Now I know our time is gone ♪
- [cell phone thuds]
["No Stress" by CMD/CTRL playing]
♪ No stress, we're wide awake now ♪
♪ Young blood erase our mistakes now ♪
♪ Buying up everything we want now… ♪
I'm gonna see
if I can call Nico from the street.
There's no service in here.
If you see him,
please tell him to wait for me.
Sweetheart, you don't think
there's a reason he won't answer?
No matter how many chances you give him
and what he says,
if you're someone's priority,
they'll show it.
And he'll treat you like dog shit
over and over again.
And you'll be like, "One day,
I bet he'll notice." [clicks tongue]
But no. It's like being invisible.
Trust me. Fuck someone else to forget him.
[scoffs] So you've got it all figured out.
For you, fucking's a way
to get away from your problems.
It's not about fucking, Chloe.
It's about building relationships.
With love, affection. Heard of it?
Guess not. 'Cause when I offer you any,
you bite my hand.
- That's not what I'm into.
- You're scared to be vulnerable.
You won't let anyone see inside you,
in case they discover
you're not as hollow as they think.
And you have to start being responsible
for your feelings.
I'm not saying this to hurt you,
but to see
if you'll wake the fuck up one day.
♪ No stress ♪
[song ends abruptly]
Oh hey!
You here to party with us?
That's not against protocol?
Uh, Joel's upstairs, right?
Yeah, why? What's wrong?
[Omar sighs]
They were dancing, that's all.
A misleading photo.
Really?
[sighs] I'm going fucking crazy.
What the hell am I doing, huh?
Either I trust him or not.
- [sighs]
- Hey, let's go for a walk. Get some air.
["Bawdy" by Shygirl playing]
♪ All now, playing games
Tell me is that what you like ♪
[elevator bell dings]
♪ I'mma have to keep you close
Throw it back, grind it right… ♪
Have you seen Sonia?
Well, actually, she just left.
She got fed up with waiting.
- [Nico sighs]
- ♪ Now, tell me, is it good… ♪
But come on in.
This bottle's calling your and my name.
♪ Like to take you home
Like to be alone ♪
♪ Not alone
Just you and me, I really need ya ♪
♪ I just wanna get down ♪
♪ Real low, yeah, I like it ♪
♪ You can bring it
Come and get it, move your body to me ♪
Uh, can I… use… use your phone?
I need to call Sonia,
and my battery ran out.
Honey, you don't think you've already done
enough damage?
- [thuds]
- Enough with that. Leave her in peace.
Just drink and be merry. Trust me on this.
- Wait, my cousin and-
- Your cousin, what?
- And Sonia.
- Sonia, what?
No, nothing.
I mean, he's the one you're into.
"He, he…"
We'll see.
You're wingman-ing
your own cousin right now?
Seriously, Nico?
No, I was just saying
it's only natural you like him.
- Uh-huh. Sure.
- Because Eric's awesome and handsome.
- He's awesome.
- The whole package.
But we'll see.
Your cousin's an incredible fuck,
but I'm sure you're even better.
♪ Running through your mind all the time ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Now, tell me, is it good? ♪
♪ Are you feeling right
Come and get up in it… ♪
Let me explain a sec.
- See, when I fuck-
- What do you need to explain, babe?
Shut up and bend me over.
♪ All these hands running over my body ♪
♪ Got me in my feelings tonight ♪
♪ Never knew someone
Could have got me like this ♪
♪ One touch, and I'm yours all the time ♪
♪ All these hands running over my body ♪
- [Chloe panting, moans]
- ♪ Got me in my feelings tonight ♪
♪ Never knew someone
Could have got me like this ♪
♪ One touch, and I'm yours all the time ♪
♪ Wait, I just wanna
I just wanna get down ♪
♪ Real low, yeah, I like it ♪
♪ You can bring it, come and get it
Move your body to me ♪
♪ Nasty, filthy, movin' your body ♪
♪ So close, so close ♪
♪ Sexy in your ear
Telling you just how I want it, babe ♪
♪ Come and get it if you need
I guarantee you'll like the taste ♪
- ♪ Nasty, filthy, movin' your body ♪
- [moaning]
♪ So close, so close ♪
♪ Nasty, filthy, moving your body ♪
[song ends abruptly]
It's too much, y'know?
It's not just Joel. It's the app.
I'm just not sure
I'm the best person for it.
- You are. You're caring and-
- But what if I don't do a good job?
And something happens to someone?
But you can't be responsible.
Not for other people.
You cannot tell anyone.
If you still stand by
your offer to help out,
I'd like to find out
who's sending these messages.
I JUST WANT TO STOP BEING INVISIBLE.
Any idea who it is?
And he'll treat you like dog shit
over and over again.
And you'll be like,
"One day, I bet he'll notice."
But no. It's like being invisible.
I have an idea.
["Manifestación"
by Bronquio & 41V1L playing]
Ciao, handsome.
I, um… I have to go to work.
Hey! You seen my cousin anywhere?
Um, uh, I haven't.
[elevator bell dings]
Nico!
[indistinct chatter]
They arrested Rocío.
They what?
I couldn't do anything.
So you ran away? And left her?
What should I have done?
Go get myself arrested?
I just wanted you to keep your nose clean
and keep yourself out of danger.
And me and my friends. Was that too hard?
What about you?
What were you doing
while they arrested her?
["Manifestación" continues playing]
I thought you might've left.
I'm so sorry for what I said earlier.
[Nico] Chloe!
I, uh, didn't do it to hurt you
but to see if you'd wake the fuck up.
I told you he's not a good person.
I thought you might need help,
but now I see
you're just a goddamn bitch and a bully.
[song ends abruptly]
[car approaching]
[sighs]
["I Know Now" by Meggie Brown playing]
PLAYLIST FOR CHLOE BY ERIC
♪ Don't make me swear it ♪
♪ Please don't make me swear it ♪
♪ I came along ♪
♪ Until I found a friend ♪
♪ Stay with me ♪
♪ I'll always do my best ♪
[door closes]
♪ Please don't make me swear it ♪
[Eric yells]
♪ And I say ♪
- ♪ I say I know now ♪
- [panting]
♪ And where I went wrong ♪
- ♪ And you say ♪
- [shouts]
♪ You say you know how ♪
♪ I could do better ♪
♪ I could do better… ♪
[whispering] I don't like fighting
with you.
♪ If I could paint the roses ♪
♪ I wouldn't stop ♪
♪ Until I had thought of something ♪
- I love you. No matter what.
- ♪ Your voice is ♪
♪ Haunting houses ♪
[gently] Me too.
- ♪ With your goodbyes ♪
- I'm scared of losing you.
♪ Please don't ♪
- [Eric sobbing]
- ♪ Make me cry ♪
[grunting furiously]
♪ And I say ♪
♪ I say I know now ♪
♪ And where I went wrong ♪
♪ And you say ♪
♪ You say you know how ♪
- ♪ I could do better ♪
- [both panting]
♪ I could do better ♪
[Joel moans]
[both panting and chuckling]
YOU'VE BEEN ADDED
TO LAS ENCINAS SELF-DEFENSE GROUP
[cell phone chimes]
CLASSES START TOMORROW .
Thank you for being our wonderful guests
on such a special evening.
But this wouldn't be a birthday
without the gift, right?
Tonight we've seen a lot of bling-bling,
but one more gem's gotta shine.
[tense music playing]
[Raúl] After everything
we've been through,
nothing'll tear us apart.
[music intensifies]
[Jessica] Ready? Strike.
Ready? Strike.
SPORTS AREA
[Jessica] Ready? Strike.
Ready? Strike.
[Raúl] Sara.
Will you be my wife?
[Jessica] Then here are your options.
Stay with him and pray to whatever god
you choose that he will keep you safe.
Or you learn to defend yourself.
In case things go wrong.
[tense music grows to a crescendo]
[tense music fades]
[somber instrumental music playing]